The fruit of that rot is here.
Violence, ugliness, derangement.
I know because I once shared that mindset.
I thought I was on the side of compassion, but I wasn't.
I was blind.
The programming we absorbed trained us to confuse cruelty with righteousness,
and we couldn't see what was right in front of us.
And here's the heart of it:
When we excuse or laugh at cruelty, when we rationalize violence as justice,
it doesn't just corrupt politics.
It corrupts us.
Without an anchor in truth, evil doesn't creep in quietly.
It takes over.
Yeah, it's shocking stuff.
And it's a pattern now.
We're seeing this happening on more and more campuses.
So at the University of California, Davis, our brave Turning Point USA chapter
was set to host Brandon Tatum as a 'prove me wrong' event.
Goes up, sets a table.
Anyone can go and have free speech and dialogue if they disagree.
And Antifa showed up full masked, black outfits.
They came in, took our gear, destroyed our tables.
Basically made the students had to flee, and the police did nothing to intervene.
Nothing whatsoever.
This is after one of our Turning Point USA students at University of Texas, Dallas,
had a bike lock thrown at her and actually had to be hospitalized for this treatment.
Sean, we are seeing a disturbing pattern from the radical left,
and we have data to now support it.
According to the National Contagion Research Institute,
48% of left of center respondents say that it's justified to murder Elon Musk.
53% say that it would be justified to murder President Donald Trump.
We have to take a step back here and ask our question.
What's really going on here?
There's a deeper thing than just political disagreement.
If you are on the front lines, like our Turning Point USA students,
you are potentially putting your safety, your well-being,
and - God forbid - your life in jeopardy, for simply being a conservative on a college campus.
If we can excuse the murder of a man for his words and call it progress,
something inside of us is already twisted.
I know, because it was once twisted in me.
And so I'll leave you with this.
If mocking the dead and excusing political murder is where our politics has led us,
then it's time to step back and ask ourselves,
not just who the real monsters are, but whether we've already become them.
In violence, great.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I have the best news ever.
What?
Oh, Donald Trump died.
Uh, second best news.
What, the president died?
Okay, third best news.
That Elon Musk died?